Git is not configured to allow long paths. This can cause issues with Shorebird's Flutter checkout. Please run 'git config --system core.longpaths true' to enable long paths.
ΓÜá shorebird login:ci is deprecated.

To authenticate in CI, create an API key at https://console.shorebird.dev and set it as your SHOREBIRD_TOKEN environment variable.

Existing tokens from login:ci will continue to work for now, but will stop working in a future release.
